in these uncertain times your top
priority is to secure the future of your
loved ones and you would want an ideal
plan for it
this is where a term life cover plan
comes in
while looking for a term plan you need
to look out for plan
that can adapt itself to fulfill your
changing responsibilities
your responsibilities change at every
stage of your life but what stays the
same is your love for your family and
the need to protect them
to best suit your needs we have
developed a new dynamic plan an all-new
term plan that will ensure the
protection of your family at every life
stage so let's secure the future of your
loved ones with icici pro i protect
return of premium return of premium a
plan option which provides life cover
during the policy term and
simultaneously ensures that you get your
premiums back on survival till the end
of the policy term
let's understand this with the help of
an example
mr sharma aged 35 opts for eye protect
return of premium with a life cover of
one crore he pays an annual premium of
938 rupees till the age of 75.
in case of unfortunate demise of mr
sharma during the policy term his
nominee will get an amount of rupees 1
crore and if mr sharma survives the
policy term at the age of 75 he gets
back 105
of the total premiums paid that is
17.6 lakh rupees
you also get additional protection
against 64 critical illnesses and
accidental death cover
so what are you waiting for make a smart
choice and secure the future of your
loved ones by opting for the right cover
at the right time while also ensuring
that you get your premiums back on
survival with our comprehensive term
plan icici pro i protect return of
premium
[Music]